{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Guest House Builders","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/62356/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62356,"taskName":"Guest House - Build","taskDescription":"Build a Guest House","xmTaskDescriptor":"Guest House Builders","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"guest house, addition, guest home, casita","textMessagingName":"Guest House Build","rolloverLongDesc":"Usually a detached structure for guests that may include a kitchen, bedroom, and bathroom. These firms are general contractors who specialize in building additions. They supply or coordinate all the relevant services including foundations, framing, plumbing, HVAC, electrical, drywall, flooring, etc.","rolloverShortDesc":"Add a guest house to a property.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build a Guest House or Casita.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Guest House Builders \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Add a Guest House or Casita","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":2,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Guest House Construction","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Guest House - Build","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Guest House Addition","urlName":"Guest-House-Build","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Guest House and Casita Builders in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"guest house, addition, guest home, casita, granny flat, mother-in-law","emcCategoryOid":-12001,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8811,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62356/":{"taskOID":62356,"originalTaskOID":62356,"setID":8811,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500766,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":201194,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Design and build","answerDisplayText":"Design and build","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201195,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Build - Use existing architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Build - Use existing architectural drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201196,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Design - Create architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Design - Create architectural drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503018,"questionDisplayText":"What type of guest house/casita addition will this be?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of guest house/casita addition will this be?","shortQuestionText":"What type of guest house/casita addition will this be?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1896,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Detached addition","answerDisplayText":"Detached addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":676,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition attached to home","answerDisplayText":"Addition attached to home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5126,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remodel existing space","answerDisplayText":"Remodel existing space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500984,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms Included:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the rooms included in this project:","shortQuestionText":"Select the rooms included in this project:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3633,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Living/Family room","answerDisplayText":"Living/Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Laundry/Mud room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry/Mud room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1846,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Deck/Porch","answerDisplayText":"Deck/Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160804,"questionDisplayText":"Requires Work on Historical Structure","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Does this project require work on a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160805,"questionDisplayText":"Request for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request for a commercial (non-residential) location?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500766,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":201194,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Design and build","answerDisplayText":"Design and build","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201195,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Build - Use existing architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Build - Use existing architectural drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201196,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Design - Create architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Design - Create architectural drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":201194,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Design and build","answerDisplayText":"Design and build","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201195,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Build - Use existing architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Build - Use existing architectural drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201196,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Design - Create architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Design - Create architectural drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503018,"questionDisplayText":"What type of guest house/casita addition will this be?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of guest house/casita addition will this be?","shortQuestionText":"What type of guest house/casita addition will this be?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1896,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Detached addition","answerDisplayText":"Detached addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":676,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition attached to home","answerDisplayText":"Addition attached to home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5126,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remodel existing space","answerDisplayText":"Remodel existing space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1896,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Detached addition","answerDisplayText":"Detached addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":676,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition attached to home","answerDisplayText":"Addition attached to home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5126,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remodel existing space","answerDisplayText":"Remodel existing space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500984,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms Included:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the rooms included in this project:","shortQuestionText":"Select the rooms included in this project:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3633,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Living/Family room","answerDisplayText":"Living/Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Laundry/Mud room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry/Mud room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1846,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Deck/Porch","answerDisplayText":"Deck/Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3633,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Living/Family room","answerDisplayText":"Living/Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Laundry/Mud room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry/Mud room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1846,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Deck/Porch","answerDisplayText":"Deck/Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160804,"questionDisplayText":"Requires Work on Historical Structure","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Does this project require work on a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":160805,"questionDisplayText":"Request for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request for a commercial (non-residential) location?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}